<resources>
    <string name="item_title">GoldReefCity</string>
    <string name="app_name">Protea Glen Tour</string>
    <string name="services">Services</string>
    <string name="chill_zones">Chill Zones</string>
    <string name="entertainment">Entertainment</string>
    <string name="food">Food</string>
    <string name="accomodation">Accomodation</string>
    <string name="ekuthuleni">Ekuthuleni, meaning at a place of peace, offers quality accommodation in Soweto. It is the ideal place to sit back and relax, whether it’s after a day out in the ever so lively Johannesburg city or a night out at one or all of the Soweto hot spots situated nearby. This double storey house has 8 bedrooms with double and single beds. The rooms are well furnished each fitted with a Tv and DStv, you cannot miss the exquisite gum tree furniture which flows from one room to the next. There is a shower and toilet in each of the standard rooms and an en-suite bathroom in the luxury rooms. As you step out of this serene establishment you are met by an always vibrant environment set right in the centre of history, with the Regina Mundi Catholic church just a 2-minute walk away. The Hector Pieterson Museum and the well renowned Vilakzi Street where the former home of former President Nelson Mandela is situated are within an 8 km distance which is a mere 15 minutes drive away. Here there are also a number of restaurants where you can dine and enjoy a delectable African cuisine. Should you want to go on a Sowetan shopping experience, the Maponya Mall is 7.5 km, just 11 minutes away. Public transport is within easy walking distance, allowing you to navigate and travel through Soweto and its surroundings with ease.</string>
    <string name="old">\'Attention all students\'\' The price will include your transport from the bed and breakfast to the Florida Unisa campus and back. Free wi-fi and breakfast. See additional cost list for airport transport. Experience old time charm with warm hospitality at this one-of-a-kind Bed and Breakfast, situated in Florida, Johannesburg which is one of the older and more historical suburbs of Roodepoort. The Old\'e Charm offers convenient and ideal accommodation for the business person and leisure traveller alike. This establishment comprises of three double bedrooms of which all have en-suite bathrooms. All rooms are equipped with clock radios fans and heathers. DStv, Compact packages conveniently located in the lounge area and displayed on a wide plasma screen. After a day of exploring the Gauteng Area, relax in and around the sparkling pool, walk about the well-established garden to discover many of the secret and hidden enclosures of the garden or entertain friends or family at the open barbeque area. The Old\'e Charm is closely situated to various restaurants, shopping malls, i.e. Westgate, Clear Water Mall and Florida Junctio. Mr Delivery is available or a dinner would be personally prepared on request at an extra charge. For the sightseeing customer, The Old\'e Charm is in close proximity of the Cradle of Humankind, various Casinos, the Lion and Rhino Park and other exciting tourist attractions. To people visiting friends or relatives in the closely located hospitals or clinics, we offer ideal overnight accommodation. Very close to Unisa campus in Roodepoort. And close to FNB Soccer Stadium. Other services offered by this charming establishment include secure parking and free WiFi.</string>
    <string name="zazas">Zazas Guesthouse and Spa offers bed and breakfast, and is situated in Pimville, which is in Soweto, Gauteng. Perfect for guests looking for stylish accommodation and pampering, away from the city\'s hustle and bustle. Accommodation at Zazas Guesthouse comprises 3 spacious suites, which are equipped with either 2 three-quarter beds, that can be configured into a king-size, or a queen-size bed. The Deluxe Suite has an en-suite bathroom that has a shower and bath. The 2 remaining suites share an interlinked bathroom that has a shower. Each room is sumptuously decorated, and contains facilities such as free Wi-Fi and a TV that has selected DStv channels, air-conditioning and a lockable dressing room as well as a complimentary beverage tray and a luxury gown with slippers. Guests can enjoy a Continental or English Breakfast offered at the guest house, and all other meals provided on request, and for those who need a bit of pampering, the on-site spa provides a variety of professional treatments including facials, massages, beauty therapy as well as a range of other services. Secure parking is available for vehicles, and guests will find an array of facilities and activities such as the Walter Sisulu Memorial in Kliptown and the Chris Hani Baragwanath Hospital as well as Lenasia Country Club and Gold Reef City Casino and FNB Stadium.</string>
    <string name="hanna">O\'Hanna\'s is your home from home. We offer friendly, professional service with our accommodation. You may be interested to know that O\'Hannas BnB was the residence of one of Florida\'s first Mayors. Upon arrival, many guests have commented that they feel as if they have entered a small village, with it\'s gardens that still retain the old world charm of yesteryear and the wide variety of bird life. We are a 3 minute walk to Florida CBD and only 2.5km from UNISA Florida Campus, close to the Main Reef Road, Industrial area, Flora Clinic and Ontdekkers Road. There are nine fully furnished rooms that have, en-suite bathrooms with showers only. Guest rooms all have private entrances, as well as tea/coffee facilities, SABC TV, electrical blankets, heaters, fans and secure parking. The guest rooms do not form part of the house. We have a laundry area that has a iron and ironing board so your clothes can stay fresh, as well as having a and microwave oven available for your use to warm up any goodies you may require to do. All rooms have various menu\'s from different food outlets in the area, such as Mr. Delivery, so you can ordered for yourself and whatever you choose will be delivered to your room.</string>
    <string name="lebo">Lebo\'s Soweto Backpackers is situated in Orlando West, a vibrant community rich in history and culture. The hostel offers a personal and unique experience with a choice of staying in dormitories or private rooms. You can also pitch your own tent or rent a fully equipped one, or stay in our cozy tree-house built with thatched grass and bamboo. Lebo\'s is proud to be 1 of the few black-owned backpackers and 1 of the few backpackers in a black community in South Africa. Head out to the famous suburb Orlando West and get a unique experience. Get to know Soweto by walking the streets and learn the township lingo, ‘Tsotsi Taal’. Join our tours, cycling or walking, play soccer with the locals and watch the big games. Volunteer in 1 of our community projects and meet people that make development happen. Take a walk to museums, restaurants and shebeens. Visit the church and sing to the gospel tunes. Visitors have use of a communal self-catering kitchen, an outdoor games area with a pool table and foosball table, hammocks, and braai facilities. Enjoy a delicious braai around the campfire and dance to the local beats from drums and kwaito music. The vibey Beach Bar is the place to listen enjoy a drink, and listen and dance to African beats and reggae rhythms. Breakfast, lunch and dinner is served in our Outdoor Restaurant. Join us under the lapa, around the boma, or just lay down on a blanket for a picnic to enjoy the sun and a home cooked meal. Authentic and delicious meals are prepared on the fire, and on the menu you find potjiekos, curries, salad buffets and the South African favourite, braais. A continental breakfast of cereals, yoghurt, fruit, juice, tea and coffee, as well as cooked breakfasts of bacon, sausage, eggs, tomato, cheese and toast are also available.</string>
    <string name="pimville">Pimville Guest House is situated in Pimville; which is 1 of Soweto\'s townships. Pimville borders the Soweto Golf course and is close to Kliptown where the Walter Sisulu Square of Dedication is situated. The guesthouse offers top class and reasonable accommodation in Soweto - Johannesburg. Pimville Guesthouse offers 6 en-suite rooms, with open-plan kitchen and visitors lounge, spacious patio with built-in braai. All rooms and lounge present a flat screen TV including DStv channels, and refrigerators. There is also secure parking available on-site. Soweto has a wide variety of activity to enjoy, from cultural visits to museums and places of history. Soweto boasts all types of restaurants and many places to socialize. There is also extreme sports for the adrenaline junkies. There are also many places of worship and conference facilities.</string>
    <string name="plekkie">Plekkie in die Son is located in Witpoortjie, Roodepoort which is a city in the Gauteng province. One of the city\'s favourite attractions is the Walter Sisulu National Botanical Garden, situated 10 km from the establishment. There are 2 guest rooms available in this 13 roomed establishment. The other 11 rooms are currently booked by long term tenants. Each room has a single bed with nightstand, linens and towels. There are separate bathrooms which are shared with other guests. A number of attractions are located within the area and include the Silver Star Casino and the Mosaic Theater which are 20 km away, the town of Maropeng where you can visit the Cradle of Humankind is 35 km away; and the Sterkfontein Caves are 25 km away.</string>
    <string name="don">Don Picasso BnB offers bed and breakfast and is situated in Johannesburg. This guest house is ideal for guests looking for a basic stopover, en route to various facilities. The house consists of 5 bedrooms and 4 bathrooms. The bedrooms are furnished with a double bed in each, and the bathrooms have a shower or bath. The house has a lounge area for guests to relax and socialise in. The lounge leads out to a private backyard, which has a firepit for guests to use. Breakfast is included and is served in the restaurant on-site. The property offers free Wi-Fi Internet connection, and secure parking behind remote-controlled gates for vehicles. Don Picasso BnB is within close proximity to Southgate Shopping Centre, Kaizer Chiefs Village, Chris Hani Baragwanath Academic Hospital, and other facilities.</string>
    <string name="dithakong">A warm welcome and personalized services await you at Dithakong BnB, whether it is a business get away, holiday or overnight retreat. This up-market establishment is located in Pimville, Soweto - in close proximity to interesting historic and heritage sites. We pride ourselves with extensive hospitality experience and ensure that all the needs of leisure travelers are fulfilled. Meals are prepared by a Chef. Security is tight and privacy is guaranteed. The establishment provides all the elegance, charm and sophisticated comfort any guest could wish for. This establishment offers 5 different types of rooms. Establishment facilities include: a braai area and secure parking. Dithakong BnB is situated within 3 km’s from Orlando and FNB stadiums, some of the 2010 participating ‘World Cup’ soccer grounds. The Apartheid Museum, Gold Reef City, Newtown and Southgate Shopping Mall are 6 km driving distance and Maponya Shopping Mall is only 3 km’s away. The famous Vilakazi precinct, Mandela Museum, Hector Petersen Memorial and Sisulu Freedom Square are only 8-10 minutes drive from the BnB. Local shebeens and restaurants such as Sakhumzi, Nambita and next door give travelers a chance to interact with locals for a hearty Soweto welcome and sharing of the rich Soweto history. Other places of interest are Cradle of Humankind and Lion Park. OR Tambo airport is 35 km drive. Spend a night with us and enjoy a truly warm South African experience and exciting - Soweto adventure.</string>
    <string name="orlando_towers">The Orlando towers bungee in Soweto adds a completely new dimension to sightseeing in this famous Johannesburg Township. Bridging the gap between adventure and township tourism, you can enjoy one of Johannesburg’s most vibrant landmarks like never before. With 100m drop to the ground, bungee jump, swing or free fall your way to the bottom.</string>
    <string name="hector_peterson">The Hector Pieterson Memorial and Museum in Soweto was erected in the early 1990\'s as a memorial to Hector Pieterson, a 12-year-old child, who is believed to have been the second school pupil shot by police during the Soweto Student Uprising on 16th June, 1976 - but the first fatality. The Hector Pieterson Memorial and Museum in Khumalo Street is a few hundred meters from the spot where Pieterson was gunned down</string>
    <string name="orlando_stadium">The Orlando Stadium, located in Soweto, is the home of one of South Africa’s biggest soccer teams, the Orlando Pirates. Orlando Stadium has been the scene of a number of important historical moments, not all of them involving sports. On June 16, 1976 thousands of black students from Soweto marched to Orlando Stadium to protest against the imposition of Afrikaans as a medium of instruction in black schools. The students intended to hold a rally and a peaceful protest at the stadium but a violent response from the police meant they never reached the stadium and the day ended in tragedy as scores of students were killed</string>
    <string name="goldReefCity">The Gold Reef City theme park in Johannesburg has some of South Africa’s fastest, biggest, most twisting and turning thrill rides. There is an abundance of adventures to be had at Gold Reef City! Join the young at heart and test-drive any of the more than thirty thrilling rides at our theme park. Whether you want family friendly, kiddies rides or the biggest adrenalin rush, there is a ride for everyone at Gold Reef City.</string>
    <string name="Maponya"><![CDATA[Maponya Mall is an enormous shopping mall in Klipspruit, Soweto, known for its beautiful fountain and life-sized statue of an elephant at its entrance. The centre is the perfect lunch stopover for those looking to explore Soweto with varied restaurants and fast food outlets available to choose from. The mall is also home to top national retailers, local businesses, as well as health and leisure venues to attract the young and old. The mall is within walking distance from the Kliptown tourism precinct, University of Johannesburg Soweto Campus, and a few minutes’ drive from the Hector Pieterson Museum and Vilakazi Street tourism precinct. Shops include Pick n Pay Hyper, Woolworths, Edgars, Mr Price, Foschini, and Clicks. You can also find stores like Ackermans, Truworths, CNA, Van Schaik Bookstore, Fashion Express, Mzanzi Designers Emporium, Franco Ceccato, Markhams, Identity, Jet, and Legit. Other features include banking facilities, optometrists, jewellery stores, medical and legal services, hair and beauty salons, and a post office. The centre houses the Boston City College, Pimville Sports & Fitness Club, Virgin Active gym, and Ster-Kinekor cinema complex. If you’re looking for something to eat, you can take your pick of News Café, Spur, Panarottis, Chicken Licken, McDonald\'s, Wimpy, Nando’s, KFC, Steers, Debonairs, and a whole lot more. There are 3,526 free parking bays for your convenience.]]></string>
</resources>
